[
  {
    "answerkey": 2,
    "option 3": "Develop new software features",
    "option 4": "Reduce software performance",
    "question": "What is the main goal of SQA?",
    "option 1": "Increase the cost of software development",
    "option 2": "Ensure software meets specified requirements"
  },
  {
    "answerkey": 4,
    "option 3": "Risk management",
    "option 4": "Marketing strategy",
    "question": " Which of the following is NOT a part of SQA?",
    "option 1": "Code reviews",
    "option 2": "Testing"
  },
  {
    "answerkey": 2,
    "option 3": "To develop new features",
    "option 4": "To deploy software",
    "question": "What is the role of testing in SQA?",
    "option 1": "To make sure the software is free of bugs",
    "option 2": "To identify defects in the software"
  },
  {
    "answerkey": 3,
    "option 3": "Testing individual components or functions",
    "option 4": "Testing the entire system",
    "question": "What does unit testing focus on??",
    "option 1": "Testing user interactions",
    "option 2": "Testing deployment environment"
  },
  {
    "answerkey": 1,
    "option 3": " Value stream mapping",
    "option 4": "Vendor management system",
    "question": " What does the V-Model in SQA represent?",
    "option 1": "Verification and Validation process",
    "option 2": " Version control system"
  },
  {
    "answerkey": 1,
    "option 3": " Testing the system's performance",
    "option 4": "Vendor management system",
    "question": "Which of the following is black-box testing?",
    "option 1": "Testing without knowledge of the internal code structure",
    "option 2": " Testing with complete access to source code"
  },
  {
    "answerkey": 4,
    "option 3": "Testing how software units work together",
    "option 4": "Testing individual functions or components in isolation",
    "question": "What is unit testing used for?",
    "option 1": " Testing the overall system behavior",
    "option 2": "  Testing user interaction"
  },
  {
    "answerkey": 1,
    "option 3": " Unit testing",
    "option 4": "Integration testing",
    "question": " What type of testing focuses on the system’s performance under heavy load?",
    "option 1": "Load testing",
    "option 2": "Usability testing"
  },
  {
    "answerkey": 2,
    "option 3": "System testing",
    "option 4": "Integration testing",
    "question": "What is the first level of testing usually performed?",
    "option 1": "Load testing",
    "option 2": "Unit testing"
  },
  {
    "answerkey": 4,
    "option 3": "System testing",
    "option 4": "Acceptance testing",
    "question": "Which testing ensures that the software meets the user’s needs?",
    "option 1": "Load testing",
    "option 2": "Unit testing"
  }

]